[CRICKETS SINGING]
[HEELS CLACKING]
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC]
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
[PEOPLE LAUGHING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
♪ HEY, DON'T WRITE
YOURSELF OFF YET ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY IN YOUR HEAD,
YOU FEEL LEFT OUT ♪
♪ OR LOOKED DOWN ON ♪
♪ JUST TRY YOUR BEST ♪
♪ TRY EVERYTHING YOU CAN ♪
♪ AND DON'T YOU WORRY
WHAT THEY TELL THEMSELVES ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE AWAY ♪
♪ IT JUST TAKES SOME TIME ♪
♪ LITTLE GIRL, YOU'RE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE RIDE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING
WILL BE JUST FINE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING WILL BE
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ HEY, YOU KNOW
THEY'RE ALL THE SAME ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU'RE DOING BETTER
ON YOUR OWN ♪
♪ SO DON'T BUY IN ♪
♪ LIVE RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ YEAH, JUST BE YOURSELF ♪
♪ IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF IT'S GOOD ENOUGH ♪
♪ FOR SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ IT JUST TAKES SOME TIME ♪
♪ LITTLE GIRL, YOU'RE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE RIDE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING
WILL BE JUST FINE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING WILL BE
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ IT JUST TAKES SOME TIME ♪
♪ LITTLE GIRL, YOU'RE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE RIDE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING
WILL BE JUST FINE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING WILL BE
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ WHOO ♪
♪♪♪
[MUFFLED MUSIC]
♪ HEY, DON'T WRITE
YOURSELF OFF YET ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY IN YOUR HEAD,
YOU FEEL LEFT OUT ♪
♪ OR LOOKED DOWN ON ♪
♪ JUST DO YOUR BEST
(JUST DO YOUR BEST) ♪
♪ DO EVERYTHING YOU CAN
(DO EVERYTHING YOU CAN) ♪
♪ AND DON'T YOU WORRY
WHAT THEIR BITTER HEARTS ♪
♪ ARE GONNA SAY ♪
♪ IT JUST TAKES SOME TIME ♪
♪ LITTLE GIRL, YOU'RE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE RIDE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING
WILL BE JUST FINE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING WILL BE
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ IT JUST TAKES SOME TIME ♪
♪ LITTLE GIRL, YOU'RE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE RIDE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING
WILL BE JUST FINE ♪
♪ EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING WILL
BE ALL RIGHT ♪
[PEOPLE CHEERING, CLAPPING]